Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
- Planetary, 1999; 9 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 10 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 11 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 1999; 12 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 13 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 14 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 15 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 17 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 18 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 19 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 20 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 21 (Box 22)
- Planetary, 2000; 22 (Box 22)
- Planetary/Authority: Ruling the World, 2000 (Box 22)
- Planetary/Batman: Night on Earth, 2003 (Box 22)
  Publisher: DC/Wildstorm
- Planetary/JLA: Terra Occulta (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 1 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 2 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 3 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 4 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 5 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 6 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 7 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 8 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 9 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 10 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2004; 11 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2005; 12 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2005; 14 (Box 22)
- Plastic Man (v.4), 2005; 15 (Box 22)
- Power & Glory, 1993; 1A (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: Howard Chaykin
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 1 (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: Peter Krause
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 2 (Box 22)
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 3 (Box 22)
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 4 (Box 22)
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 35 (Box 22)
  Notes: Crossover with Starman 39-40
- Power of Shazam!, 1995; 36 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1984; 1 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1984; 2 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1984; 3 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1984; 4 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1984; 5 (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: Mary Wilshire
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 6 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 7 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 8 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 9 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 10 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 11 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 12 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 13 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 14 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 15 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 16 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1985; 17 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 18 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 19 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 20 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 21 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 23 (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: John Bogdanove
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 24 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 25 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1986; 26 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 27 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 28 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 29 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 30 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 31 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 32 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 42 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 43 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.1), 1987; 44 (Box 22)
- Power Pack (v.2), 2000; 1 (Box 22)
  Author: S.C. Bury
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 9 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 10 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 11 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 12 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 13 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 14 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; 15 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 16 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 17 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 18 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 19 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 20 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 21 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 22 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 23 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 24 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 25 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 26 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2002; 27 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2003; 28 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2003; 29 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2003; 30 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2003; 31 (Box 22)
- Powers (v.1), 2001; Ann. 1 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 1 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 2 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 3 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 4 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 5 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 6 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 7 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 8 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 9 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1995; 10 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 11 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 12 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 13 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 14 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 15 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 16 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 17 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 18 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 19 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 20 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 21 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1996; 22 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 23 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 24 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 25 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 26 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 27 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 28 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 29 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 30 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 31 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 32 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 33 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1997; 34 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 35 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 36 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 37 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 38 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 39 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 40 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 41 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 42 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 43 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 44 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 45 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 46 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1998; 47 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 48 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 49 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 50 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 51 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 52 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 53 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 54 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 55 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 56 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 57 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 58 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 1999; 59 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 60 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 61 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 63 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 64 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 65 (Box 22)
- Preacher, 2000; 66 (Box 22)
- Preacher Special: Cassidy: Blood and Whiskey (Box 22)
- Preacher Special: One Man's War, 1998; 1 (Box 22)
- Preacher Special: The Story of You-Know-Who, 1996; 1 (Box 22)
- Primal Force, 1994; 0 (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: Ken Hooper
  Notes: Zero Hour event
- Primal Force, 1994; 1 (Box 22)
- Primal Force, 1994; 2 (Box 22)
- Primal Force, 1994; 3 (Box 22)
- Private Beach, 2001; 1 (Box 22)
  Author: David Hahn
- Private Beach, 2001; 2 (Box 22)
- Private Beach, 2001; 3 (Box 22)
- Private Beach, 2001; 4 (Box 22)
- Private Beach: Fun and Perils in the Trudyverse, 1995; 1 (Box 22)
- Private Beach: Fun and Perils in the Trudyverse, 1995; 2 (Box 22)
- Private Beach: Fun and Perils in the Trudyverse, 1995; 3 (Box 22)
- Pro, The, 2002 (Box 22)
  Artist/Penciler: Amanda Conner
- Promethea, 1999; 1 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: J.H. Williams III
- Promethea, 1999; 2 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 1999; 3 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 1999; 4 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 1999; 5 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 6 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 7 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 8 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 9 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 10 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 11 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 12 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 13 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 14 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 15 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 16 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2000; 17 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 18 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 19 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 20 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 21 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 22 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 23 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 24 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 25 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 26 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 27 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 28 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2001; 29 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2002; 30 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2002; 31 (Box 23)
- Promethea, 2002; 32 (Box 23)
- Punx, 1995; 1 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Claude St. Aubin
  Publisher: Valiant
  Notes: valiant
- PVP, vol. 2; 10 (Box 23)
  Author: Scott Kurtz
  Artist/Penciler: Scott Kurtz
- Raphael, 1 (Box 23)
  Author: Kevin Eastman, Peter Laird
  Artist/Penciler: Kevin Eastman, Peter Laird
  Notes: Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles spin-off; irregular-size, 2 copies.
- Rawhead Rex, 1993 (Box 23)
  Author: Clive Barker, Steve Niles
  Artist/Penciler: Les Edwards, Hector Gomez
- Rawhide Kid, 2003; 1 (Box 23)
  Author: Ron Zimmerman
  Artist/Penciler: John Serverin
  Publisher: Marvel/MAX
- Reign of the Zodiac, 2003; 1 (Box 23)
- Remarkable Worlds of Professor Phineas B. Fuddle, 2000; 1 (Box 23)
  Author: Boaz Yakin
  Artist/Penciler: Erez Yakin
  Publisher: Paradox Press
- Remarkable Worlds of Professor Phineas B. Fuddle, 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 1 (Das Rheingold), 2000; 1 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 1 (Das Rheingold), 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 1 (Das Rheingold), 2000; 3 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 1 (Das Rheingold), 2000; 4 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 2 (The Valkyrie), 2000; 1 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 2 (The Valkyrie), 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 2 (The Valkyrie), 2000; 3 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 3 (Siegfried), 2000; 1 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 3 (Siegfried), 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 4 (Götterdammerung), 2000; 1 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 4 (Götterdammerung), 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 4 (Götterdammerung), 2001; 3 (Box 23)
- Ring of the Nibelung, Book 4 (Götterdammerung), 2001; 4 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1992; 1 (Box 23)
  Author: Chuck Nixon
  Artist/Penciler: Tom Lyle
  Notes: Bagged collector's ed.
- Robin III, 1992; 2 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1992; 3 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 4 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 4 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 5 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 5 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 6 (Box 23)
- Robin III, 1993; 6 (Box 23)
- Rogan Gosh, 1994 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Brendan McCarthy
- Rom, 1984; 56 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Bright
- Rom, 1984; 57 (Box 23)
- Rose, 2000; 1 (Box 23)
- Rose, 2000; 2 (Box 23)
- Rose, 2001; 3 (Box 23)
- Sachs & Violens, 1993; 1 (Box 23)
- Sachs & Violens, 1993; 2 (Box 23)
- Sachs & Violens, 1994; 3 (Box 23)
- Sachs & Violens, 1994; 4 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1983; 1 (Box 23)
  Author: Marry Jo Duffy
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1983; 2 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1983; 3 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1983; 4 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Ricardo Vilamonte
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 5 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 7 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 8 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 9 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 10 (Box 23)
- Saga of Crystar, Crystal Warrior, 1984; 11 (Box 23)
- San Diego Comic Con Comics, 1994; 3 (Box 23)
  Notes: compilation multiple artists and writers
- San Diego Comic Con Comics, 1995; 4 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 1 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Sam Kieth
  Notes: Master of Dreams
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 2 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 3 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 4 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 5 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 6 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Dringenberg
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 7 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 8 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 9 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 10 (Box 23)
  Notes: The Doll's House
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 11 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1989; 12 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 13 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 14 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 15 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 16 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 17 (Box 23)
  Notes: Dream Country
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 18 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 19 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 20 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 21 (Box 23)
  Notes: Seasons of Mist
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 22 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 23 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1990; 24 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 25 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 26 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 27 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 28 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 29 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 30 (Box 23)
  Notes: Distant Mirrors, 2 copies.
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 31 (Box 23)
  Notes: Distant Mirrors
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 32 (Box 23)
  Notes: A Game of You
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 33 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 34 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 35 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1991; 36 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 37 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 38 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Duncan Eagleson
  Notes: Convergence
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 39 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 40 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 41 (Box 23)
  Notes: Brief Lives
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 42 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 43 (Box 23)
  Notes: Brief Lives, 2 copies.
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 44 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 45 (Box 23)
  Notes: Brief Lives, 3 copies.
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 46 (Box 23)
  Notes: Brief Lives, 2 copies
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 47 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1992; 48 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 49 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 50 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 51 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Alec Steven
  Notes: World's End
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 52 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 53 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 54 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Michael Allred
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 55 (Box 23)
  Artist/Penciler: Shea Anton Pensa
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 56 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 57 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 58 (Box 23)
  Notes: The Kindly Ones
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 59 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1993; 60 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 61 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 62 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 63 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 64 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 65 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 66 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 67 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 68 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 69 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 70 (Box 23)
  Notes: The Wake
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 71 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1994; 72 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1995; 73 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1995; 74 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2), 1995; 75 (Box 23)
- Sandman (v.2) Special, 1991; 1 (Box 23)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 4 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 5 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 6 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 7 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 8 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 9 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: R.G. Taylor
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1993; 10 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 11 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 12 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Steven T. Seagle
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 13 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 14 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 15 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 16 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 17 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 18 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 19 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 20 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 21 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; 22 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 23 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 24 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 25 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 26 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 27 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 28 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 29 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 30 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 31 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 32 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 33 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1995; 34 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 35 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 36 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 37 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 38 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 39 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 40 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 41 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 42 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 43 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 44 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 45 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1996; 46 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 47 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 48 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 49 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 50 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Daniel Torres
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 51 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 52 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 53 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 54 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 55 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 56 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 57 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1997; 58 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1998; 59 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1998; 60 (Box 24)
- Sandman Mystery Theatre, 1994; Ann. 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Bast, 2003; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Joe Bennett
  Notes: three issue limited series
- Sandman Presents: Bast, 2003; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Bast, 2003; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Everything you always wanted to know about dreams...but were afraid to ask, 2001; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Love Street, 1999; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Love Street, 1999; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Love Street, 1999; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Lucifer, 1999; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Lucifer, 1999; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Lucifer, 1999; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Merv Pumpkinhead, agent of dream, 2000 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Petrefax, 2000; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Petrefax, 2000; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Petrefax, 2000; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Petrefax, 2000; 4 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Corinthian, 2001; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Danijel Zezelj
- Sandman Presents: The Corinthian, 2001; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Corinthian, 2001; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Dead Boy Detectives, 2001; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Dead Boy Detectives, 2001; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Dead Boy Detectives, 2001; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Dead Boy Detectives, 2001; 4 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Thessaliad, 2002; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Thessaliad, 2002; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Thessaliad, 2002; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: The Thessaliad, 2002; 4 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Thessaly: Witch for Hire, 2004; 1 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Thessaly: Witch for Hire, 2004; 2 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Thessaly: Witch for Hire, 2004; 3 (Box 24)
- Sandman Presents: Thessaly: Witch for Hire, 2004; 4 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1993; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Scott Eaton
- Scarab, 1993; 2 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 3 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 4 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 5 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 6 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 7 (Box 24)
- Scarab, 1994; 8 (Box 24)
- Scars, 2002; 1b (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Jacen Burrows
  Publisher: Avatar
  Notes: "a" and "b" after issue numbers indicate front-only or wraparound covers
- Scars, 2002; 2b (Box 24)
- Scars, 2002; 3a (Box 24)
- Scars, 2002; 4a (Box 24)
- Scars, 2002; 5b (Box 24)
- Scars, 2002; 6a (Box 24)
- Scary Godmother: Bloody Valentine, 1998 (Box 24)
- Scatterbrain, 1998; 1 (Box 24)
- Seaguy, 2004; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Cam Stewart
- Sebastian O, 1993; 1 (Box 24)
- Sebastian O, 1993; 2 (Box 24)
- Sebastian O, 1993; 3 (Box 24)
- Secret Origins 80-Page Giant, 1998; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Angel Unzueta
- Secret Wars II, 1985; 1 (Box 24)
  Notes: See also Marvel Super-Heroes Secret Wars. 2 copies.
- Secret Wars II, 1985; 2 (Box 24)
  Notes: nine issue limited series
- Secret Wars II, 1985; 3 (Box 24)
- Secret Wars II, 1985; 4 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 1 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 2 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 3 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 4 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 5 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 6 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 7 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 8 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 9 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 10 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1996; 11 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1997; 12 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1997; 13 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1997; 14 (Box 24)
- Seekers: Into the Mystery, 1997; 15 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1991; 31 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1991; 32 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1991; 33 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1991; 34 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 35 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 36 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 37 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 38 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 39 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 40 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 41 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 42 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 46 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 47 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 48 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1992; 49 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1993; 50 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1993; 51 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1993; 52 (Box 24)
- Sensational She-Hulk, 1993; 53 (Box 24)
- Sergio Aragonés Destroys DC, 1996; 1 (Box 24)
  Artist/Penciler: Sergio Aragonés
- Seven Miles a Second, 1996 (Box 24)
  Author: David Wojnarowicz
- Sgt. Fury and His Howling Commandos, 1964; 13 (Box 24)
- Shade, The, 1997; 1 (Box 24)
- Shade, The, 1997; 2 (Box 24)
- Shade, The, 1997; 3 (Box 24)
- Shade, The, 1997; 4 (Box 24)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 1 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 2 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 3 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 4 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 5 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 6 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1990; 7 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 8 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 9 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 10 (Box 25)
  Artist/Penciler: Bill Jaaska
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 11 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 12 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 13 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 14 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 15 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 16 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 17 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 18 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1991; 19 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 21 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 22 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 23 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 24 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 25 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 26 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 27 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 28 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 29 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 30 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 31 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1992; 32 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 33 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 34 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 35 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 36 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 37 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 38 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 39 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 40 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 41 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 42 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 43 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1993; 44 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 45 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 46 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 47 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 48 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 49 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 50 (Box 25)
- Shade the Changing Man (v.2), 1994; 51 (Box 25)